Da la lun dun
BABY I'mma MONSTER
Mano a mano
I see you in slow mo'
You know you're in trouble
Ooh hoo hoo hoo
발버둥 쳐봐
어차피 손바닥
위에서 못 나가
You know that
눈을 뜬 순간 피어나
All eyes on me 불을 질러라
Do or die
On my life
Yeah you ain't seen nothing yet
Got them all going
Sheesh Sheesh
Sheesh Sheesh Sheesh yeah
B.A.B.Y.M.O.N
Sheesh Sheesh
Sheesh Sheesh Sheesh yeah
Got them all going
Yo hold on 쉿
걍 들이부어라 네 달팽이관에
이건 네 귀에 줄 축복
음악에 맞춰 걍 춤 춰
히비리 합 합 boom boom pow
분위기 타올라 너네들 눈 돌아
띵하니 적잖이 충격일 거야
Crown this queen
홈런은 쳤고 내 다음은 위
어중이떠중이 중간 아님
날 보고 닫혔던 입들 say
Sheesh Sheesh Sheesh
You know what it is
I be running this
Pull up in a ghost
Peek a peek a boo hoo
Vroom vroom
너네 심장에 박동이 pump pump pop
Pedal to the metal
Click clack click
Put'em up to the sky
High high high high
눈을 뜬 순간 피어나
All eyes on me 불을 질러라
Do or die
On my life
Yeah you ain't seen nothing yet
Got them all going
Sheesh Sheesh
Sheesh Sheesh Sheesh yeah
B.A.B.Y.M.O.N
Sheesh Sheesh
Sheesh Sheesh Sheesh yeah
Got them all going
마음껏 웃어봐
이젠 내 차례니까
천천히 불태워 네가 잠든 사이
Time's up 올라가 올라가 더
꼭대기 꼭대기로
하늘 위 하늘 위로
Fly away
온 세상을 뒤집어
Come on let's ride
BABY I'mma MONSTER
B A B Y M O N
Tell a friend tell a friend
tell a friend
B A B Y M O N
Tell a friend tell a friend
tell a friend
Let's go
Jump jump and let it go
Watch out we on a roll
Rum pump pump pump it up then
Jump jump and let it go
Watch out we on a roll
Rum pump pump pump it up then